

# **Ming-Yang Ho**



ikaminyou@gmail.com

github.com/Kaminyou

linkedin.com/in/kaminyou

+886 952792255

## Summary ·

A data scientist at aetherAl with 4+ years of experience in 2D/3D computer vision, natural language processing, machine learning, and deep learning algorithms development. Besides, I am also adept at web programming, cryptography, and clinical pharmacy.

### Skills

- Programming related
  - Python
  - PyTorch
  - •C/C++
  - ReactJS
  - MySQL
  - Docker
  - Linux
  - •Git
- Domain
  - Machine learning
  - Deep learning
  - •2D/3D computer vision
  - Natural language processing
  - Cyber security
  - Computer security

## Language -

- Mandarin (native)
- •English (TOEIC 825) [2014]
- Japanese (JEPT N1) [2021]

### Interests

#### Machine learning, Deep learning, Full stack development, Computer security

### Work experience

#### **Data Scientist**

aetherAI, Oct. 2021 - (Current)

#### **Teaching Assistance (TA)**

NTU EE Machine Learning, Feb. 2021 - Jul. 2021

NTU EE Web Programming, Feb. 2021 - Jun. 2021

NTU CSIE Bioinformatics and Cheminformatics, Sep. 2020 - Jan. 2021

#### **Data Engineer Intern**

Dcard, Jun. 2020 - Dec. 2020

- •Built an automatic image cropping system to attract users' attention.
- •Invented a malicious applicants detection system with SimCLR.
- Established a system to immediately detect offensive comments.

#### Software Engineer Intern

Institute of Information Science, Academa Sinica, Jul. 2019 - Aug. 2019

•Leveraged the concept of RGB channels to assist in SNP prediction.

### Honors

#### 2021 PyCon APAC Speaker

Get 3D models out of nothing: Python implementation of deep learning-based 3D models reconstruction from 2D images..

#### **PyCon TW Speaker**

Implementation of a deep learning-based saliency detection system by Python

### 2020 HITCON Speaker

Potential Security and Privacy Issues in Novel Taiwanese National eID system

### **Awards**

2022 Best thesis award

2021 Multi-label Classification on CT Medical Imaging Competition, 3rd prize

ICH detection enhenced by asymmetric loss with CNN-LSTM approach.

### **Recent Projects**

### **SUPERB: Speech processing Universal PERformance Benchmark** Entrusted by NTU, CMU, MIT, and Facebook AI to build a leaderboard web

server for SUPERB Benchmark. (https://superbbenchmark.org/)

### 2021 Template is all you need: 2D to 3D reconstruction with template learned by contrastive learning

Developed a 2D to 3D reconstruction DL model leveraging the template concept.

### **Education**

#### 2019~2021 Master of Science (@CSIE CMDM lab) GPA 4.2 (Best thesis award)

Research topic: 3D computer vision, Machine learning, Computer security

Computer Science (bioinformatics specialization)

BEBI, EECS, National Taiwan University (NTU)

Look, Listen, and Diagnose: a deep learning based comprehensive Parkinson's disease evaluation system with 3D point cloud and acoustic features

#### 2014~2019 Doctor of Pharmacy GPA 4.1 (CS-related GPA: 4.3, Outstanding Graduate Award) \*Also got admitted to NTU CSIE. Clinical Pharmacy

School of Pharmacy, National Cheng Kung University (NCKU)

by deep learning-based 3D estimation. [unpublished manuscript]

### **Publications**

Ho, M. Y., et al. (2022) Ultra-high-resolution unpaired stain transformation via Kernelized Instance Normalization. [under review]

\*Ho, M. Y., \*Liu, L. C., Su, B. H., Wang, S. Y., Hsu, M. T., & Tseng, Y. J. (2021). PanGPCR: predictions for multiple targets, repurposing and side effects. Bioinformatics, 37(8), 1184-1186. (\*equal contribution)

Ho, M. Y., Kuo, M. C., et al. (2022) Look, Listen, and Diagnose: a deep learning based comprehensive Parkinson's disease evaluation system with 3D point cloud and acoustic features. [unpublished manuscript] Ho, M. Y., Kuo, M. C., et al. (2022) A 2D camera is all you need: gait analysis with frontal-view 2D video